Matt Walsh and Nick Carter are partners
at Castle Island Ventures. All views
expressed by them or the guests on this
podcast are solely their opinions and do
not reflect the opinions of Castle
Island Ventures. Guest and host may
maintain positions in the assets
discussed in this podcast. You should
not treat any opinion expressed by
anyone on this podcast as a specific
inducement to make a particular
investment or follow a particular
strategy, but only as an expression of
their personal opinion. This podcast is
forformational purposes only. Brought
down by Bad Mortgage Investments,
Lehman, which has 25,000 employees, will
be liquidated. The federal government
loans American International Group AIG
$85 billion.
>> This is A DIFFERENT KIND OF MARKET AND
THE FED IS ASLEEP.
>> The federal government is stepping it to
stabilize Fanny May and Freddy Mack, the
two mortgage giants that have been
threatened by the housing crisis.
>> The Bank of England has pumped 75
billion pounds more into Britain's
ailing economy with a new round of
constituted easing.
>> You print a couple trillion dollars and
all of a sudden people start to worry.
So out of this worry, we have something
called a Bitcoin.
>> Welcome to On the Brink. I'm Matt Walsh.
And I'm Nick Carter.
>> I had a terrible, terrible travel 24
hours.
>> Yeah. You're looking a little frazzled,
actually.
>> Yeah. I mean, I'm in the same clothes I
was wearing uh over 24 hours ago, right?
I came right to the office. So, I went
down to New York for a day trip. I had a
I don't know 8:00 flight back. And uh I
stayed at the at LaGuardia until about
midnight and then they canled the
flight. All the airport hotels were
booked. So, I ended up in a Roach Motel
in Flushing and I had a 6 a.m. flight,
went to the airport, that was cancelled
and I had to take the train. So, you had
to take the Uber at rush hour into
downtown.
>> Yeah. Well, it wasn't really R. It was
before rush hour, but yeah, was still
wasn't great. Also had just no clothes.
So, it's the life we lead. People say
this is an easy job.
>> Was the TSA working or are they kind of
like on strike or something? No, TSA was
good.
>> Oh, cuz I heard the TSA is like broken
right now.
>> Oh, really? No, I got through fine. TSA
was not not my problem. It was the fact
that they were saying there was bad
weather in Boston and it's not that bad.
>> Yeah. Spirit of thought for all the uh
crypto folks just they can't fly.
They're into Dubai and now they they get
trapped.
>> Oh, I know. That's bad.
>> That's tough. That's a good good portion
of the crypto industry is there.
>> Yeah, I know. Yeah. Hopefully everyone's
staying safe. So I guess it Yeah, could
be worse.
>> Yeah,
>> could be a lot worse.
>> No uh Cast Island content this week.
>> No, we'll be back next week with a few
pods, but some interesting deals this
week.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Big chunky one to lead
us off. Cast, which is the stable
coinbased card payments platform. They
raised 60 million from QED Left Lane
Peak 15 partners and others. Huge round
there.
>> That's a big round. Then we have Zodel,
which is the Zcash Open Development Lab.
This is a company that is building at
the protocol level in Zcash and I
believe also have a wallet. Uh they
raised 70 uh $25 million, sorry about
that. Um from Paradigm, Andre Crypto,
Coinbase Ventures, and a number of
others. This is kind of the the spin-off
team, right?
>> Yeah. I haven't been following Zcash
politics that closely. I guess there
seems to be a lot of internal conflict
in the Zcash ecosystem. There was it was
the guy from Cosmos was in Zcash for a
while and then there was a split. It
seems like this is where the momentum is
with this zodle entity.
Then we have very AI. Uh this is a
platform to verify human ownership of AI
agents 10 million from Polychain,
Anagram, and others. Big congrats to
Zach and the team over there. Then it's
Arc Labs which is a Bitcoin DeFi
platform. They raised $5 million from
Tether, Ego Death, and Anchorage
Digital.
Crypto is an institutional crypto
accounting platform. They raised $45
million from Blackfin Capital, Sentinel,
Global, 1KX, and Blue Yard. And lastly,
it's UTEXO, which is a Bitcoin native
stable coin payments platform. They
raised 7.5 million from Tether, Big
Brain Holdings, Portal Ventures, and
Maven 11.
>> Tether getting involved there. Vote of
confidence, I guess, for Bitcoin. Not.
There have been a lot of Bitcoin native
stables. No breakout successes so far, I
would say.
>> Yeah. Not yet. Tether's uh deploying a
lot of capital. Feel like in the deals
of the week, we're saying Tether quite a
bit.
>> So, I think we have to acknowledge the
elephant in the room, which is are we
entering some kind of prolonged oil
crisis, do you think here?
>> Well, how long is the straight of Hormuz
going to remain closed, I guess, is the
question.
>> I think it can be closed indefinitely. I
I don't actually think because we had
this issue with the Houthies was the
last year.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Pretty rag tag militia and they were
able to was it the Red Sea that they
were targeting shipping in the Red Sea.
So I think if Iran wants they can keep
the straight shot as long as they want.
>> I don't know. I don't know if you can I
guess all it takes to disrupt the
straight is one guy kind of with a
rocket launcher, right? But
>> yeah, with a shoulder launched miss
anti-ship missile, like that's the
thing. I think people think you need
ships and mines. I don't think so. I
think you can launch a missile from
inland.
>> Yeah. I don't know. At some point
though, don't you think China, who's
receiving most of that oil, starts to do
something about it?
>> Yeah, I do. And uh I think one thing
people don't realize is the US is the US
is number one producer of oil in the
world or oil plus natural gas.
Domestically, the US would actually be
fine in some ways if the it wouldn't be
catastrophic if the straight stays
closed because we're not really getting
the oil from there. But Europe suffers,
Japan and Korea and China suffer if it
stays closed. And obviously the oil
producers in the Gulf suffer.
So it's kind of scary territory. Scott
Bessant has said he this just came out.
He said it was always part of the plan
for the US Navy to escort tankers.
But are they actually doing that right
now?
>> No, as of right now. No.
>> So yeah, they might have to start doing
that. You also wonder what that's going
to do for interest rates here. So if
oil's trading at, you know, 110
throughout the summer, that's going to
be a tough call on cutting rates, I
think.
>> Yeah. I mean, some people are now
thinking the energy shock could tip us
into another inflationary episode like
the 70s.
>> Yeah. I'm actually a bit more
optimistic,
believe it or not. But I can understand
why why markets of the jitters right
now.
>> Trading these um oils uh contracts on
hyperlquid seems to be what a lot of
people in our industry are doing.
>> Yeah, it is funny. The peak of uh the
crude price was the exact day that oil
was listed on Binance.
>> Is that right? Wow.
>> Yeah,
>> that's perfect. That's like every token
that ICOs on Binance just straight down.
classic pattern.
>> Binance just takes 8% of the supply. Do
they just get 8% of all the oil? Is that
how that works in that country?
>> Something like that.
>> They give it to their VIP insiders and
just dump it into oblivion. That's
that's the Binance way.
>> So yeah, speaking of Binance, they are
suing the Wall Street Journal apparently
for defamation uh regarding
the WSJ's reporting on Binance's uh
compliance failures. Is that right?
>> Yeah. Proving defamation is going to be
really hard, don't you think? enormously
hard in the US. Very, very high bar to
meet. And also, the defense is the
truth. So, if the WSJ was reporting
accurately, then doesn't matter that
it's damaging that they're in the clear.
There's a Fortune article this week on
Binance and some of the moneyaundering
allegations there. There's a ton of
detail. I mean, if there's an
explanation to this, then Binance should
get out in front of it. But, you know,
they have uh the ages of the people,
where they apparently were said to live,
what type of ID they uploaded. There's
an unbelievable amount of detail on
these alleged moneyaundering violations.
>> Yeah. I mean, I just wouldn't be
surprised if there was substance the
allegations. And I will say sentiment
seems to have turned sharply against
Binance. It really doesn't help that the
compliance was loose, that they fired
apparently the compliance officers that
found this. And of course 1010 does not
help.
>> Yeah, 1010 we still don't have a great
explanation of what happened there, but
at minimum we know that Binance the way
they had the um index price calculation
and feed was wrong. And so they they
made the situation worse.
>> Yeah. So they need to get their house in
order. Domestically,
NASDAQ and Kraken announced a
partnership to bring equities fully
onchain via Kraken's X stocks platform
designed to give holders of tokenized
shares the same rights as any other
common shareholder. Thought that was
really interesting. Of course, last week
we talked about Intercontinental
Exchange investing in OKX. This week you
have NASDAQ and Kraken. You think it's
more of a trend here, you know, the
Tradfi exchanges coming in doing
partnerships with the crypto venues?
>> Yeah, I think so. I I think um you know
fast forward 10 years
you know the default way the default
brokerage people use will be one of
these hybrid crypto
uh traditional platforms whether it's a
Coinbase or a Robin Hood or Kraken. So I
think it makes sense just to have stocks
natively on those platforms and um I
think it makes a lot of sense. I mean,
it's just we obviously have to iron out
some of the details, but it seems to be
the form factor that people want.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Certainly, there's a
distribution advantage to going and
pairing up with some of these
cryptonatives if you want to play in the
retail game, right? So, the interesting
thing is a lot of these exchanges,
that's not really their business to
begin with. They're almost like seat
model type of exchanges, a B2B motion,
whereas the Krakens, the OKXs of the
world are retail brokers basically. And
so it's it's almost like a vertical
integration play for some of the legacy
exchanges. So on the regulatory front,
huge amount of news this week. I don't
even know where to start. The SEC and
the CFTC had anou. They're going to
formally coordinate oversight of digital
assets. Basically, the way I read this
was the turf war between kind of a day
taunt in the turf war between the two
agencies.
>> Yeah. Which is good to see. So you had
um Celig and Atkins went on um went on
Shimath's podcast, Allin podcast um and
talked about this a little bit. I mean
this is this was part of the tension
under Gensler, right? He was sort of
always behind the scenes elbowing out
the CFTC and people thought that he was
trying to make a a turf war battle to
take over the CFTC which of course
Gensler ran at one point. So, it's good
to have that because there are a lot of
these cases in our industry where it's
unclear whether or not the token is a
security or a commodity and you just
need to have, you know, a lot of
dialogue, I think, between those two
agencies. There's going to be trading
venues that have securities and
commodities side by side to each other,
and you don't want to have duplicative
uh dual registration efforts if you
don't have to.
>> Yeah. I one thing that I found
particularly interesting was the two
agencies are going to collaborate on
market surveillance. So with infor uh
information sharing, joint oversight,
coordinated investigations. Meanwhile,
you have the CFTC's division of market
oversight. They released their guidance
on prediction markets, calling on
exchanges to engage with the agency
prior to listing contracts that might be
vulnerable to manipulation. Think about
it. The SEC is the main agency that
deals with market manipulation inside of
trading. It looks like the CFTC's
enforcement function is being beefed up
here. specifically with an eye to
prediction markets.
>> Yeah, this was a really interesting one
on the CFTC side um with prediction
markets because as we know these markets
are not doing this right now. Like do
you get the sense that Khi and Poly
Market are getting actively involved in
trying to uh go through an approval
process to list these markets and make
sure that they're not ripe for
manipulation or insider trading. Like at
least on the poly market side, this is
just a free-for-all.
>> Yeah. I mean, I think they have probably
some
analytic function to investigate
uh, you know, suspicious
heavy betting patterns, accounts that
are freshly funded and make bets right
before the markets settle or before they
swing one way. The thing is, these
platforms are just going to have to
build this capability
because either the regulators will
demand it or there'll just be dozens of
these kind of insider trading events. So
they'll have to get good at this.
>> You're just going to see a turf war here
for the next few years between CFTC and
the state attorneys. I think you're
going to see a lot of lawsuits from the
state ages that don't want this in their
states. One market that I think we're
going to see insider activity on or if I
had to guess would be the Oscars because
of course there's people with privileged
information right as to the winners.
Isn't it what like KPMG or Deoid or
whoever does the like they get the names
ahead of time? Is that what you're
talking about?
>> Yeah. Yeah. I mean, so you know, a
certain number of people will know,
right?
>> Yeah.
>> And one of them might be tempted. These
are going to be liquid, very liquid
markets because there's a lot of
interest in them.
>> When are the Oscars?
>> Couldn't tell you, but uh there is a
whole feature on Poly Market.
>> Who's up for best picture? Uh, one
battle after another is the overwhelming
favorite right now. 77%.
>> I've never heard of it. Have you seen
that?
>> It was the Paul Thomas Anderson movie
with Leo. I didn't I haven't watched a
single one of the candidates. Uh, the
second favorite with 20% is sinners
followed by Hamnit. Hamnit is was
actually pretty good. That's the only
one I saw.
>> I haven't even heard of any of those.
I'm very out of the loop on cinema. I
haven't been to the movies in like 10
years. I
>> actually recommend Hamnit. about
Shakespeare.
It's uh his son, that was his name,
Hamnet. But apparently back in those
days, the N and the L was the same
letter. Really? Did you know this?
>> No, I didn't know that.
>> And so then he wrote the play Hamlet Lit
and he named it after his son who died.
Not to spoil the movie.
>> Oh, all right.
>> But it's actually quite good.
>> All right, I'll have to look at that.
Everyone keeps on telling me I need to
watch Age of Disclosure. Have you seen
that yet?
>> No.
>> Alex Thorne was talking about that on
his podcast. Go listen to Galaxy Brands
this week. They talk about UFOs on
Galaxy Brains.
>> Oh, it's a UFO thing.
>> It's a UFO thing. Apparently, it's good.
>> So, elsewhere, Ripple announced a $750
million buyback that values the
company's equity at 50 billion. Wow,
that's a big number there. Impressive.
Next one up is a cross protocol. This is
a cross-chain bridging protocol. They
launched a governance vote and they're
considering sunsetting the token and the
Dow structure in favor of actually
becoming a US corporation with more
traditional equity ownership. I would
think that you might try to see more of
these actually. Yeah. You know, every
time this has happened, I've thought to
myself, well, I think there'll be many
more. And then there just haven't been.
Like, do you remember um Iconomy from
2018 or something? That was a that was a
big ICO, wasn't it?
>> They did something like this. I think
they were may arguably the first ones to
try this and I at the time I thought,
well, a lot of these tokens are just
going to do that and convert the tokens
into equity. Maybe now it'll actually
happen. I think maybe now is is the
right time. Yeah, very interesting.
We'll be monitoring this one.
>> So, I kind of struggle with this a
little bit because on one hand, you're
like, "Okay, that makes sense. It should
just be a security token depending on
what the token actually does. this Dow
structure clearly doesn't work for a lot
of these um formats. But then when you
dig into some of these that are thinking
about going private quote unquote, the
revenue that they generate is not much,
right? So you have, you know, let's say
you have a million dollars a year in
transactional volume. What type of
multiple would you get on that from a
valuation perspective? So I think you'll
end up seeing a bunch of these protocols
that are worth $20 million market cap
and they think going to equity will
increase the value. It's like no
actually you probably just bring the
value down to like5 or $7 million for
your equity. Yeah, I agree that almost
certainly a multiple compression story
and also logistically, how do you take
20,000 globally distributed token
holders, presumably some of them retail,
and then give them an ownership interest
in a US security? That's the hard part.
>> No, you don't. And I think you kind of
have to hope that a lot of people have
those coins on wallets that they lost.
And I suspect you'll see some
shenanigans where the teams will say,
"Okay, if you don't claim the tokens in
90 days, those go those reverse accrete
back to the company."
>> Yeah. So that's the one thing I've never
seen anybody solve elegantly.
>> It's not solvable, right? Because in a
private company, you're capped at um how
many shareholders you can have. So
unless you put together some SPV
structure and you can let these people
in, but even at that, you're going to
have a lot of nonacredited, right? So, I
think the accredititor investor laws
actually stand in the way of this really
working.
>> This could be something for the SEC to
think about.
>> They should. I mean, on that podcast,
actually, the All-In podcast this week,
they talked a little bit about the
accredited investor protection laws,
which are really just don't work. I
mean, they really keep people that are
below a certain income level down. Like
I remember for the longest time when I
was kind of getting into this industry,
I was well below the accredited
threshold in terms of income. And I just
thought that was crazy. It's like I'm
pretty qualified to to look at some of
this stuff.
>> Yeah, there should be uh some kind of
skills-based qualification as opposed to
just means
>> Yeah. I don't know, like a test or
something, but I guess always a test
could get gameable. You don't want to
put like a bunch of bureaucracy around
and do series 7 and make people come in.
But yeah, there's got to be something
>> not very elegant. The Ethereum
Foundation has begun staking a portion
of its treasury with Bitwise. Bitwise
onchain solutions, new infrastructure
for institutional grade staking with
plans to stake up to 70,000 ETH.
>> Bitwise is cranking. We're we're
obviously investors there, so big fans
of what they're doing. But between the
asset management arm and the new uh
staking arm. So they bought a testant
and then Chorus Swan. So they're they've
become one of the largest staking uh
companies as well. So did you see Micro
Strategy bought more Bitcoin this week?
So they bought $1.28 billion worth of
Bitcoin this week.
>> And that's that's based on their uh
perpetual instrument, right?
>> It seems like that perpetual instrument
is is what's driving it. Yes. um they
now have 3.5%
of the um total supply of Bitcoin.
>> Well, at least someone's buying. The
White House released Trump's cyber
strategy for America. Um does talk about
blockchain infrastructure also mentions
postquantum cryptography as a priority
for the admin.
>> Now I saw some mixed things uh on that.
So on one hand people are saying well
the prior admin actually had more
concrete dates around quantum and um
seemed a little bit more worried about
it. Did you read that into it?
Yeah I've saw I've seen this commentary.
My view is that the core transition
dates from NIST are unchanged. Uh it's
still
you know 2030 is when
uh most agencies are instructed to start
deprecating legacy cryptography
and some high risk high value uh
strategic agencies have to actually
basically complete their transa uh
transition by then. 2035 is the target
date for full migration across the whole
government. That's unchanged.
The the level of, you know, noise the
administration is making about it is
maybe a little bit less, but I don't see
any real change. One interesting thing
to track is DARPA's QBI, quantum
benchmarking initiative. This is the
most rigorous attempt to kind of figure
out when uh when and if a quantum
computer will be built a you know major
one I expect that they'll have their
preliminary results by 2027 2028.
So even if one is not built by those
dates we will have a very good sense of
the timelines.
>> That's very interesting. Well, we'll
keep an eye on that. I mean, the funding
doesn't seem to be slowing down
whatsoever into the quantum space.
>> No, there have been a bunch of new
listings both here and in Europe
and uh yeah, I mean my my view remains
uh that it's, you know, a pretty
near-term concern and it's just an
engineering challenge at this point.
Scott Aronson keeps repeating that. So
there's some forthcoming research that
uh project 11's going to put out that uh
will be extremely precise and very
technical which we'll share when it's
ready. In other news this week, uh
Commissioner Hester Pur at the SEC put
out some remarks um that touch on
tokenization actually. So touches on a
number of categories, but one of the
things she said is that the SEC is
working on a narrow innovation exemption
to allow the limited trading of some
tokenized securities rather than a
broader exemption which was contemplated
in the draft recommendations. Um I think
she my read here is that she's skeptical
that creating new rules are actually
required that the SEC can actually just
do a lot of this under existing rules
for tokenized securities which kind of
makes sense. Um, she closes it and we'll
put this in our uh newsletter, so
subscribe there if you want to read the
full take here. But I think the gist of
it is like, hey, we have securities laws
and if these things are securities,
they should just kind of fit into the
laws, which I get, right? Like if
something goes from T+2 to T+1, you
don't need to like write a new law. It
just happens. It's just better
technology.
>> Yeah, that makes perfect sense. I think
the um I think the question here is
going to be on some of these no action
letters and how broad they're going to
be. I don't think that you're going to
just get blanket no action relief on
categories. I think it always has to
kind of be case by case uh specific. So,
one thing we forgot to mention is the
BPI, not the Bitcoin policy institute,
but the bank policy institute. Uh they
represent the big banks. They're
considering suing the OC over the bank
charters that have been granted to
crypto and fintech firms. That includes
Circle, Ripple, and Bridge.
>> This BPI, man. So JP Morgan, one of the
biggest backers of the BPI, and shout
out JP Morgan, just just awful posture
towards this industry as usual. The head
of the BPI makes over $3 million a year,
and he co-wrote a book with Gary
Gensler. So that's all you need to know
about him.
>> Jeez.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. They're kind of sore losers, the
banks. Although what's interesting is at
the same time they're kind of planning
for what looks like an inevitable
future. You saw Wells Fargo filed a
trademark for WFUSD.
>> I saw that.
>> Implies maybe they're hedging a little
bit here.
>> Well, if you're a smart bank, I mean,
you have to do something, right? The the
snowball has started here on this
industry. You're going to have tokenized
securities. Banks are allowed to touch
the underlying. Stable coins exist in
the world. They will be a thing. You
have startup companies that are growing
much much faster than the money center
banks in terms of money movement. So the
banks have to do something. I think
there's going to be a real dividing line
between the banks that innovate on their
business model, release stable coins,
get into global FX for stable coins, do
tokenized securities, run ATS venues,
run dark pools on tokenization
uh projects. Um and then those that just
don't do anything. I think you will see
deposit flight from banks that are are
just absent from the industry. But
>> you know what's funny is the banks that
have been protesting
the provision, you know, the yield
provision and clarity and so on that
have been trying to stop stables
offering interest. They don't have a
good explanation for why there has not
been meaningful deposit flight given the
existence already of yieldbearing stable
coins or of kind of high yield checking
accounts offered by these neo banks or
fintexs.
>> That's the interesting thing, right?
>> I don't see the harm as of right now.
>> So that's a a very important point. So
stable coins and the yield dynamics
exist today. So it's not like the crypto
industry is asking for something that
hasn't already been passed ingenious and
that has been existing in this country
for a long time. So if the deposit
flight was going to happen, it would
have already happened.
>> Yeah. the discerning
customer, whether a CFO of a startup or
a ordinary retail individual, they
already have access to these high
yielding instruments whether through a
money market or a stable coin. So,
but it's clear that there is a se, you
know, whole cohort of trillions of
dollars that are willing to accept the
loss on the yield uh in exchange for the
efficiency of being inside a large
banking institution. So, it seems fine
as the status quo seems fine. I guess,
you know, if I was to play devil's
advocate on that and talk against the
position, I would say, look, if
everything goes 24/7 in terms of
trading, that'll probably end up trading
against not a bank dollar, but against a
stable coin because you can't move the
bank dollars on the nights and the
weekends. And so, that's a big chunk of
activity, right? anyone who has a
brokerage account or wants to trade
24/7. If you need stable coins in order
to actually do a trade on a Saturday,
you're going to and you can make some
money on the stable coin, you're going
to hold stable coins. So, it's valid.
>> Yeah. No, I agree. Look at interactive
brokers turning on stable coin deposits
247. I think that's fascinating.
>> Yeah. It's And it's more than just like
sending them in, right? It's okay. If
you want to buy Apple, you have to have
a stable coin to buy it.
like the market itself I think will be
stable coin denominated.
>> The other risk that I think banks do
face here is just the general
acceleration of deposits and
withdrawals. So this was already you saw
this in the 2023 crisis. We saw the
fastest rates of bank runs ever in
history by a lot with SBB for instance
100 billion in withdrawals in a single
day because you have online banking and
mobile banking. Now imagine how much
faster it will be once banks do embed
stable coins fully.
I think that's a that's a kind of true
and salient concern, but it's not the
concern that the banks are raising and
>> actually like what entitles the banks to
this net interest income anyway. It's
purely a function of the Treasury rate.
So it's like, hey, we yeah, we have this
monopoly from the federal government
that we just need to print money every
year based on the interest rate and the
spread there. Like
I don't think that should be a monopoly.
We're not talking about these FinTechs
coming out and doing fractional reserve
banking. They're not actually trying to
compete with your direct business model.
They're just trying to use the US
dollar. Yeah. And you talk about people
being upset about bailouts for the banks
in08.
This
franchise that the banks maintain an
iron grip on, they print a quarter
trillion dollars a year on the interest
margin. So, it's just a never-ending
rolling bailout for the banks. So I who
could possibly be in favor of that aside
from the banks.
>> The banks and the banks have the most
powerful lobby. I was down uh in New
York as I mentioned yesterday and was
with a group of people that were asking
me about the just the fight here between
the industry and the bank lobby and
who's going to win. And my take is look
the bank lobby is pretty powerful. It's
way more powerful than the crypto lobby
at this point. And they're super
entrenched with the senators. So, you
know, to the extent that a deal happens
here, it's probably going to look a
little bit closer to what the banks want
than the crypto industry wants. But I
don't think that's the right thing.
Yeah. And it was funny because even this
compromise of paying yield on
stablecoin payments like some kind of a
rewards for payments like an interchange
model. Even that is controversial.
>> You know, it's good to have something to
unite against though, right? as an
industry, you know, we had Gensler, we
United, we had FTX, we really didn't
like Sam. Um, now we got the the Bank
Policy Institute and Jamie Diamond.
>> Yeah. And I want to give props to
Coinbase for holding the line on this on
behalf of the whole industry. It's it's
kind of punk rock of Ryan Armstrong.
He's not the guy that people often call,
you know, a cipher punk or anything, but
is uh he's showing a lot of backbone by
doing this.
>> Yeah. I mean, he's in the Davos getting
uh profanities laced at him from Jimmy
Diamond, right? And he's he's hanging in
there for us.
>> Yeah. Good for him, honestly.
>> When do uh when do you think we get one
of these Bank Policy Institute like
things? You know, we have Fairshake.
We've got the political side of it, but
when do we get the trade group that just
works behind the scenes covertly with
the head guy makes a lot of money, but
he's a secret pawn of Gary Gensler and
Elizabeth Warren, but he makes $3
million a year.
>> Yeah. I think the problem is that we are
very fractious industry and we have a
lot of internal divisions.
>> I think we could get behind like a Jake
Turvinsky, some kind of person like
that.
>> Yeah, we're also political outsiders as
an industry. So, we have to spend big to
get anyone to care. So, I think it just
comes with time.
>> Time and jobs. We got to create many
more jobs. I think the banks have that.
They have armies of human beings. So
that's the politicians take that into
account. I think
>> speaking of quantum Kathy Woods uh
ArchInvest just came out and said
quantum computing is a long-term risk
for Bitcoin but not an imminent threat.
I guess we'd agree with that.
>> Yeah, I bet uh even if the threat's not
imminent, the urgency to act is actually
imminent. And I think that's the thing
people miss because it's not an
overnight adjustment. So, and it's
really a function of do you want the
transition to be rushed or do you want
it to be done fully and in a careful way
with a minimal loss of funds. So, even
if it is 10 years away, you probably
want to start very soon because
everybody has to migrate, everyone. So,
you just want to give people time to do
that.
>> I've always been more of a panic early
person myself. you know, you see some
COVID cases and you just go and buy a
ton of toilet paper. One of those down.
>> Also, what's the downside? There's not
really a downside. You know, there's
plenty of uh cryptographic functions
that are that are secure. Uh we could do
hashbased signatures today. So, why not
give people the opportunity to start
migrating then? That mllifies a lot of
the concerns. Wall Street is less
worried. You show that you're doing
something. I don't see a lot of upside
in just denying the risk entirely.
Denying it outright, all that means is
you're just going to have a rush
transition later. That's all that means.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Might as well just get ready
early. All right. I think that is it for
the week. Everybody have a safe and
healthy weekend and we will see you on
Monday.