Matt Walsh and Nick Carter are partners
at Castle Island Ventures. All views
expressed by them or the guests on this
podcast are solely their opinions and do
not reflect the opinions of Castle
Island Ventures. Guest and host may
maintain positions in the assets
discussed in this podcast. You should
not treat any opinion expressed by
anyone on this podcast as a specific
inducement to make a particular
investment or follow a particular
strategy, but only as an expression of
their personal opinion. This podcast is
forformational purposes only. Brought
down by Bad Mortgage Investments,
Lehman, which has 25,000 employees, will
be liquidated. The federal government
loans American International Group AIG
$85 billion.
>> This is A DIFFERENT KIND OF MARKET AND
THE FED IS ASLEEP.
>> The federal government is stepping in to
stabilize Fanny May and Freddy Mack, the
two mortgage giants that have been
threatened by the housing crisis.
>> The Bank of England has pumped 75
billion pounds more into Britain's
ailing economy with a new round of
constituted easing.
>> You print a couple trillion dollars and
all of a sudden people start to worry.
So out of this worry, we have something
called a Bitcoin.
>> Welcome to On the Brink. I'm Matt Walsh.
>> And I'm Nick Carter. Do you think this
is the best backdrop of a live Well, I
guess we're not live, but we're in
person together. Is this the best place
we've ever recorded the podcast?
>> It's a quite a picture location, dare I
say.
>> We are overlooking the water in Key West
right now.
>> The Gulf of America, in fact, is what
we're looking at.
>> This is the Gulf of America that we're
looking at right now. So, we are at the
Castle Island offsite. Been a productive
few days here.
>> Yeah, we've uh we we figured out uh you
know, who's going to win a Gent
payments.
>> We figured out where we're deploying
capital. We're going to keep it a
mystery. Um, yes, but we are open for
business, so hit us up.
>> Talk about a busy week. Oh my gosh, this
Vanity Fair thing we got to talk about.
I'd also just like to start this off by
giving a shout out to our listeners um
at Colony Pizza in Fairfield.
>> We have a a rabid fan base down there.
>> Is that Connecticut?
>> That's in Connecticut. Yeah.
>> So, we have fans reportedly in
Connecticut.
>> Fans in Connecticut. And I'm hearing
that the Colony pizza is very good.
>> So, now what kind of pizza is it? I've
been told it's a bar pie, which you know
I like the Southshore bar pie, the thin
pizza.
>> You have brought this up and I still
don't know what that is.
>> I think we should try to do something
with Colony pizza. Also the Lynwood and
Randolph which is the best.
>> All right. So, um I think this was one
of the funniest weeks ever.
>> This Vanity Fair thing. I don't even
know where to start. I mean, do we have
to set it up? I guess we should, right?
Not everyone's going to have seen this.
>> I was almost in it. It's how would you
describe it to someone who hasn't read
this?
>> So,
crypto people love to kind of just put
their foot in their mouth at really
inopportune moments and uh yeah, I mean,
Vanity Fair went out to some of the most
famous crypto people and did a photo
shoot seems, you know, innocuous enough,
but they it ended up taking on kind of a
ghoulish tint. And uh I think it, you
know, it may have been pitched to the
crypto people as a pro- crypto spread
and it ended up being like a mockery
basically.
>> Yeah. It was kind of like look at these
clowns in this clown industry.
>> Yeah. So the uh journalist Claraara, she
asked me to be on it.
>> I'm so happy you didn't do this.
>> And uh I didn't do it because I don't
really think that I photograph very
well, frankly.
>> Oh. Oh, contr. Oh, contr. Um, but I also
don't own like crazy outfits like so
like there were some serious people in
this photo shoot. I mean Kathy Wood,
Novagratz,
Melton was on it, Olaf from Poly Chain.
So like these are like real heavy
hitters. But um
the, you know, the photographer just
made them look kind of scary and like
like they're in a dungeon. So how was it
pitched to you? I have the email here. I
have the email. Hi, my name is Claraara
Molot and I'm a writer of Vanity Fair.
I'm working on a big feature on the most
important people in the crypto world.
The thesis is that there's a large group
of young successful people who've been
cast as outsiders by civil society and
especially Democrats, which is
ridiculous because their financial and
political power is only growing. I've
been cleared to have this be a
multi-page spread with a big photo
budget so I can dive into who the
players are, what their lives look like,
and how they imagine the future of
crypto. The aim is to move away from the
narrative of these people as grifters or
super conservative.
>> Oh, so that's I think that was a bait
and switch.
>> Yeah. I mean, and I actually took a
couple calls with her, too, and it was
it was very clear she viewed this or
represented it as like taking the side
of the crypto industry. Let's do this
really cool sexy photo shoot. You guys
will look cool. You'll be in Vanity
Fair. You'll have a ton of clout. But it
whether it was her decision or her
editors,
the deliberate choices were made to make
these people look like clowns,
>> right? Also, the tint, everything is
tinted green, so everybody looks ill.
>> Yeah. Did you see Dennis Bertram's um
analysis of this?
>> It was great. I didn't know he used to
be a photographer.
>> Yeah. So, he kind of broke down the
photos and said, "This is kind of how
they're trying to demean this person.
This is why it's taken from this angle."
Seems like I mean, I guess this is an
art.
>> Yeah. So, my lesson that I took from
this is just you unfortunately cannot
trust journalists. and I deal with lots
of great journalists, but if it's
someone's reaching out to you out of the
blue and you haven't dealt with them
before, you can't trust that they're
going to do right by you because it's
not necessarily an iterated game. You
may think, "Oh, I'll be a valued source
for this person for years into the
future, so they're going to be good to
me and they're not going to try and
screw me over in some way." You actually
can't trust that. It only works if you
have a real relationship with the
person. Can we talk about Olaf's gloves
here? Do you see these gloves?
>> Yeah, he's got some kind of fingerless
gloves on.
>> What's the purpose of a fingerless
glove? Isn't your fingers are the part
of your hand that gets the coldest?
>> Well, yeah. And it didn't really seem
like it was that cold in there.
>> Didn't seem like it was cold. I mean, I
like the look of these gloves. If they
were actual gloves, then I might even
own a pair of these. I think the
individual in this story that came off
worst was uh Devin Fenzer of Open C.
>> Yeah. What you know OpenC what they
raised at a north of a$13 billion
valuation. I don't hear much about OpenC
these days and they just canceled their
token sale.
>> So yeah, I mean it's just really bad
timing to cancel your token sale and
then do a photo shoot where you're
appearing in like couture with your
wife.
>> Yes.
You just got to read the room.
>> Read the room. Well, I don't know. I
This didn't do any favors for the
industry.
>> Yeah. I mean, I found I thought Meltum I
feel like she just didn't take it that
seriously and that was the right
approach.
>> That might have been the right approach
to this. Yeah.
>> All right. Let's talk about some deals
of the week. Huge one to start. BVNK, a
stablecoin payments infrastructure
company. They're required by Mastercard
for 1.8 billion. It's 1.5 billion with
300 in contingent performance-based
earnouts. Um, very impressive. And I
guess this kind of explains why
Mastercard walked away from the Zero
Hash deal.
>> Yeah. Wow. What a another big big uh
stable coin M&A deal. Many to come, I'm
sure, in the category.
>> And Mastercard kind of has a ways to go
to catch up to Visa. So, to me, it makes
sense. you know, there's some value
there just bringing over a team that
knows what they're doing in the stable
coin space because frankly Mastercard
doesn't have that.
>> Well, the weird thing is they've been
piloting stable coin stuff since 2021.
>> They just didn't get anywhere with it.
Right.
>> So, uh, next up we have Iron Light.
Their tokenized securities marketplace
21 million from the SE Foundation, Laid
Law Private Equity, the former TD Bank
CEO Greg Bracka and others. Then it's
DTC Pay which is a digital payments
platform. They raised $10 million from
Vert.ex Ventures.
>> Transf stablecoin infrastructure
company. They raised 19 million from the
touring financial group.
>> And then Republic which is um a lot of
things I guess but they're also pretty
active in the onchain investments uh
space. They received a strategic
investment from Hamilton Lane big asset
management firm there.
>> So there were quite a few pieces of
news. I mean I guess there is a gigantic
war going on but that is not really the
focus of this podcast. So
>> doesn't have a huge impact on the
digital asset markets I suppose but
definitely a big impact on the world.
>> The main point of insection is that
crypto traders are trading crude oil on
hyperlquid.
>> That is that is for sure.
>> I think they're losing money actually.
>> It is kind of interesting that you can
trade these markets 247. Um, I would
have to think that some of the bigger
players in the commodities trading
market are looking at hyperlquid as
maybe a way to express a view.
>> Well, I think it makes sense because if
you grew up on crypto, you don't want to
go to interactive brokers and learn how
to trade commodities markets, right? You
just want to do it in your sandbox.
>> Plus, you can lever it up.
>> Yeah.
>> So, people like leverage, especially in
the retail market. So, that's a huge
thing that's going on, but uh you know,
we have more important things to cover.
So, Abra, the crypto RI and wealth
manager, they're going public in a $750
million spa deal.
>> And then Kraken came out this week and
they are um said to be shutting down
their IPO plans for now. They cited
market conditions. Um but about a month
ago, they parted ways with their CFO.
So, I wonder if it was more than just
market conditions. It's you got to have
a CFO to go public. And seems like once
that announcement was made about a month
ago, you could have predicted this.
>> Yeah. And most of those publicly traded
crypto names, aside from the very
biggest ones, have had a very tough last
6 months. I mean, look at Gemini.
>> They have, but I think don't you think
Kraken will be a much bigger company in
the public markets? I mean, I would be
surprised if this is a 1520 billion or
business. Gemini is subscale.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Tough one. Obviously, we
have a lot of friends over there. Uh,
I'm sure they'll get another bite at the
apple, though.
>> Definitely the windows closed for now
for most companies, I think, going
public, but it'll it'll open back up.
Um, big news this week was the SEC
released interpretive guidance um very
detailed um on how tokenized securities
are going to work. So, they came out and
they actually explicitly called out
tokens that are not securities. First of
all, I think it was a list of 16, a lot
of um big names on there. So, it's good
to know for sure. in the eyes of the SEC
that for instance Salana is not a
security, avalanche is not a security
>> and Ripple got the
>> yeah Ripple is not a security. Um so now
you know that guidance is out that is
sort of the law of the land so to speak.
They also codified a framework for
tokenized real world securities. So, you
know, a lot of people I think have been
talking about market structure bill and
saying, "Look, we need Clarity Act. We
need to know how tokenized securities
work." And that's true, but we've always
been saying even if you don't get the
bill, the SEC has pretty wide latitude
here to form this market and this is
what they're doing. So, I super super
encouraging. Yeah, it was kind of a
bittersweet moment reading this because
the uh the commentary that James Baloney
at the uh SEC wrote, he wrote a letter
and he says this closes the final
chapter in the book of Howie. And we've
been obsessing over Howie for a decade.
>> Yeah.
>> And now Howie's gone.
>> I thought Matt Lavine had a, you know,
as usual, kind of an interesting take on
this, saying that this is the clarity
that we could have used, you know, eight
years ago when all these ICOs were being
punted out. And now that we have it, it
feels a little bit anticlimactic. It is.
This is the type of news that you'd
expect the market to be up like 40% on.
>> Yeah. But for a lot of these things that
we kind of suspected were going to be
treated as commodities, getting the
ratification, it doesn't do that much
for us. It's nice to have.
>> It's nice to have. I think the bigger
thing is just giving a framework for
taking things that exist in the real
world and tokenizing them or creating
net new types of securities that you can
put on chain. And this guidance went a
long way in defining what that needs to
look like.
>> Yeah. So, we have we settled the debate
yet as to whether we're just going to
have the same structures that exists in
Tradfi, they'll just happen to be on the
blockchain or whether we're going to
have completely new interpretations of
what a security is in a bare asset
context.
>> I think we're going to have both. I I
think you're going to have the listed
equities market and the treasury market
probably look a lot similar to the way
things work today. You might just see
the DTC using Canton and things like
that. But I think this guidance gives
pretty wide latitude for net new types
of securities to be introduced and think
about the market structures that don't
have a very defined market structure. So
think about private funds, think about
private equity, private credit where
these things don't kind of centrally
clear and settle. I think that's the
more interesting thing. And the SEC has
also left the the door open to have
public blockchains actually be the the
conduit here. So to have these things
tradable um on decentralized protocols,
which I I think is great.
>> Yeah. And something has to give cuz you
can't have rag NMS
>> and VBO on DeFi.
>> No, you can't. But you also don't need
those things to trade like LP interests
and funds,
>> right?
>> Um, so there are certain that some of
those laws only make sense for listed
public equities.
So there was maybe a compromise reached
uh between the banks and the crypto
lobby on the stable coin yield issue
which has dominated the clarity
discussions. Where did we land on that?
>> So all of this is just a reaction to
Senator Cynthia Lumis' tweet basically
saying that there's a there's progress
talks are in a delicate state basically
saying that there's been some sort of
understanding. The rumor is that you can
pay quote unquote yield or rewards, I
guess, is a better way to say it, but it
cannot be tied to the account balance. I
don't know what that means in practice.
>> The only thing it could presumably be
tied to would be your spending activity.
>> Could be spa spending activity. Maybe it
also could mean if you're a subscriber
of a product or you're paying a some
sort of a SAS fee, you can engage in the
rewards. Like if you have Coinbase One,
maybe you're eligible for rewards. But
to the balance,
>> how do you determine how much reward
gets paid out?
>> I don't know. I mean, maybe there's a
>> there's got to be some back doors here
probably. But
>> to have some sort of a compromise is
encouraging. It does look like the
markup though in Senate banking is not
going to happen until May. So, we're
kind of running out the clock a little
bit here.
>> Yeah. And it seems like there's other
legislative priorities emerging, too.
>> Yeah. Well, there's Yeah, there's a lot
of
>> the fact that the TSA doesn't seem to be
working anymore.
>> TSA, shout out to Logan Airport. Worked
great for me.
>> I keep seeing horror stories. It's like
if you go to take a flight, there's a
one-third chance that the airport is
just not functioning.
>> Oh, is that right?
>> Yeah, like uh Newark.
>> Yeah, all the New York airports are just
terrible right now.
>> Case in point, my drama from last week.
So, uh, Nater Al-Nagi, the founder of
BitClout and Basis, uh, formerly known
as Basecoin, the SEC dropped their case
against him.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh, so they'd alleged he had
raised 257 million in an unregistered
security sale. And weren't there
allegations that he had kind of
embezzled the money, too?
>> Yeah, it was a pretty long complaint. um
they tracked flows of funds and you know
there were things hitting his personal
account. He had a tweet um talking about
being debanked. So I wonder how much of
that was just that the maybe the company
lost access to banking and he was doing
a lot of that himself. I don't know if
we have the full story there. He said
he's going to go on a bunch of podcasts
and tell the story. Maybe we should have
him on.
>> Yeah. So he did have a long tweet where
he said
operation choke point was real. Right.
>> Yeah. Which I don't doubt. I mean, I'm
sure he lost all sorts of bank. This was
like a highly risky project that could
have theoretically lost bank accounts in
any um regime.
>> Yeah. So, is he implying that what
looked like embezzanine was just the
necessary mingling of corporate and
personal banking because he couldn't get
corporate banking?
>> That's what I wondered. Yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> That's what I wondered. But he also came
out and said that the um so the investor
that apparently
the SEC was hanging their hat on some
investor alleging impropriety and he
said that that was kind of a
manufactured thing where the SEC had
just been sending all these subpoenas to
investors in this project and identified
something that they thought was an
impropriety and then kind of lined up
that investor as if they were going
after them. But he said that was never
the case. He said he was in dialogue
with that investor. They didn't feel
wrong. I wonder what the full story is
there.
>> Yeah. Hard to tell.
So he's he's kind of went 0 for two, I
think, for his gigantic big fundraisers.
Do you think he he he's going to take
another swing at it?
>> I wouldn't I don't know if I'd call it
for two because I think in a lot of ways
it was smart of him not to launch basis
because that could have been Teral Luna
before Teraluna. He might have just kind
of sobered up on that idea and then he
returned capital. So, I think you he
actually acted very prudently on that.
BitCloud was sort of one of the original
web 3 social projects,
>> but it just wasn't good.
>> I don't think it was terrible. I I mean,
it was a very early kind of friendster
style thing, but
>> Well, I mean, it was We've seen it with
Friend and
>> Yeah, Friend was the other one. There
were like 50 others I think and where
you could trade you know your friends or
whatever. It just it doesn't seem to be
a good model right?
>> It might not be a good model but um I
don't think you can really
you can't accuse him of not being
ambitious. I thought it was a
>> Yeah. No, the the ambition is there. So
he seems keen to do something else. I
mean another nine figure fund raise you
know.
>> Yeah. I mean I look he very clearly has
not defrauded anyone. So
>> um all right in other news uh Phantom
very popular wallet they've received a
no action letter from the CFTC. Uh it
allows them to offer their users
regulated derivatives and prediction
market contracts without registering as
an introducing broker. That's really
interesting. So theoretically, I think
this could set a precedent uh that going
forward non-custodial wallets will not
be viewed or regulated as
intermediaries, which is we've fought
this battle on how many different
legislative fronts at this point. I
mean, I I feel like they're always
trying to jam language into these bills
that say that these um non-hosted
wallets actually need to register as
broker dealers, and this is saying no,
you don't.
>> Yeah, that is uh it's really cool to
see. Uh a lot of news this week about
strategy. So they have bought another
22,000 Bitcoin this week for 1.5
billion. 75% of it was funded with the
issuance of STRC stretch
>> which pays a yield of 11.5%
pretty good.
>> And you ask how is this yield being
paid? You know Micro Strategy has cash
on the balance sheet. I think they have
two years of cash on the balance sheet
at least. But they're just paying that
off the balance sheet. And I guess the
bet here is that the price of Bitcoin
goes up and they can continue to issue
more um at the money offerings. They
trade at a premium.
>> Yeah. So the yield would be funded by
what? Common stock at the end of the
day.
>> Yeah, I guess. I mean, right now it's
just funded by um by the cash on the
balance sheet, but they're hoping that
they start to trade at a premium to NAV
and they can continue to print more
equity. Um it's it's kind of scary to
think about where the price of Bitcoin
would be if micro strategy wasn't such a
big player in this market over the past
call it eight weeks. I think we need to
come up with new nomenclature around
this because I think what we need to do
is normalize
not calling something yield if it
doesn't derive from real economic
activity. Is that fair?
>> Yeah. So where like yield
>> generally comes from you know uh I'm I'm
offering you a debt instrument and
there's the you know cost of there's a
time value of money and I'm taking some
kind of risk on you defaulting and so
on. So there's a kind of like a real
reason for there to be yield in that
>> if I give you a loan. But in this case,
it's just kind of shuffling money
around.
>> It is a preferred security though. So
technically, I think it is kind of no
different than when Goldman did a
preferred deal with Buffett,
>> right? But but you know, there's some
kind of real corporate activity
happening under the hood. You know,
there's like revenues and so on.
>> Yeah. And in I guess you're saying that
strategy has a nent software business
that doesn't spit off a lot of cash.
>> No, it's not. But that's not what's
funding the yield. The yield is funded
through financial engineering happening
somewhere else in the capital stack.
>> Yeah,
>> I think we just can't call that yield. I
mean, it's it's like a dividend being
offered effectively, but I just don't
consider that a yield couched in real
economic activity.
>> I would feel a lot better about Bitcoin
overall if Sailor wasn't 3.5% of total
supply and if he wasn't the relentless
bid in the market. If there were others
here. I where do you think Bitcoin would
be if it wasn't for sale right now?
>> Yeah. No, it would be a tough tough look
right now. Forward Industries, that's
the Salana Dat. They've initiated $27
million stock buyback via loan from
Galaxy Digital. This is the inverse of
the DAT trade. You you know, initially
you issue shares to buy a token. Now
this is the opposite. You're selling the
token effectively to buy back shares.
How do you think these dats will be
impacted with the kind of the world
where we move away from quarterly
reporting for publicly traded companies?
It looks like the SEC is about to say
you can report twice a year if you want
to. That actually might be better for
debts.
>> Yeah, the less reporting the better for
them frankly.
>> I would think so. So Tempo, that's a
stripe back payments blockchain. They
launched mainet this week and the
machine payments protocol. This is their
Aentic payments framework. It's an
alternative to X42.
Uh pretty exciting actually. Congrats to
them.
>> I think Stripe is just making all the
right moves when it comes to payments. I
think they have a real shot of taking on
Visa and Mastercard. If you combine
Tempo with what they have with Bridge
and then you add the cards, they're, you
know, they're going to be playing in
that market as well. I think there's a
real possibility that they emerge as
almost like a third network here and
it's going to be powered by public
blockchains. Stable coins riding on
tempo basically.
>> Yeah. Especially as I think there was a
judicial decision recently that will
challenge interchange
and plus agentic payments. If I had to
pick one company it would be Stripe.
>> What what are you most bullish on with
Aentic Payments? What categories of
payments?
I think virtually all payments are going
to be agentic eventually.
Uh especially ecom, without a doubt,
ecom. I mean, think about the way you
spend money. Wouldn't you just rather
tell the agent what kind of thing it is
that you need? Um some like consumer
household good or even groceries. I buy
my groceries online. I would rather not
do that manually. Right.
>> Yeah. But I can do that with groceries
now. It's just click reorder of
something that you bought last week,
right?
>> Yeah, but I don't want to do that.
>> So, you just wanted to buy your
groceries programmatically. You're going
to have to have in
>> Yeah, I want to do it without consulting
me just as needed.
>> I have a hard time thinking through that
one because some weeks I don't need baby
diapers.
>> No, no, no. But the it looks at your
fridge. You know, you have an API
connecting your fridge camera to
>> maybe I don't know. But then sometimes
you're like, okay, I I don't need
cashews this week. You know,
>> I think uh high ticket consumer like um
travel, right?
>> Finding the best flight.
>> Travel is a big one. So, okay, I'm going
to Rome. I need a flight rental car.
Optimize this for points. I've got these
many points here, that many there. Uh
here's where I want to be. Uh go ahead
and do it. I think that would be a
perfect case.
>> I think that would be good. I think um
paying for APIs could also be a really
interesting one. And so you're building
an app and as opposed to having another
subscription to a data business or
something, you just pay programmatically
based on API usage and you're just
making small payments to get the data.
To me, that's easy, right? Just machine
to machine almost.
>> Subscriptions are good because what you
want with you want to be able to tell
your AI, can you review all of my
subscriptions? You can see who build my
card last month.
>> Are there subscriptions that I'm not
using? Look at my email. see am I
opening or subs this newsletter that I'm
subscribed to? Am I even reading it?
>> Right?
>> You know, automated management or go
renegotiate my cable subscription. Tell
Verizon that I'm going to cancel and get
the 10% discount. So, just relentlessly
optimize.
>> Yeah,
>> that those kinds of things are very
promising.
>> Content creators, this could be
interesting. Small payments. Um almost
like the everything we talked about with
Lightning. Yeah, I do think it's too
early to tell whether it's going to be
on the blockchain or if you could just
do it um in a web two way. I mean I why
wouldn't you know Visa and Google and
everyone have their own uh protocol for
agents?
>> Well, because there's no barriers to
entry to having an Ethereum address or
having a you know any public blockchain
address. There is a barrier to entry to
get set up as a merchant on the Visa
network. Yeah, but Visa is of course
obviously going to have their own
agentic framework. They're not going to
just not do this, right?
>> I just think from the ease of setting it
up, let's say we live in a world where,
you know, a few years from now, you have
a hundred agents that are doing things
for you. It would be so much easier to
spin that up on an embedded wallet with
a blockchain as opposed to registering
all those agents with Visa. I think
you're going to want reversibility with
your agentic payments because you might
not fully trust the agent.
>> That's possible. I think reversibility
is something that is unsolved in the
context of stable coins. I'm not sure
it's solvable actually right now.
>> No, we don't. I think we need a natively
reversible stable coin.
>> Circle's been talking about
reversibility. I don't know if they
actually have put out a spec on that
yet, but yeah, that is an issue, right?
So, the agent goes rogue and starts
making a bunch of payments. But that's
where I think you just have workflows.
You say, "Look, if it's a payment over
$100, I need to actually sign or, you
know, flash a an email to me that I
click yes on."
>> Yeah. I see a lot of horror stories of
people signing up for cloud services and
then they get build 100,000 by accident.
>> Yeah.
>> Because they just use too many credits.
>> I have an old AWS thing set up that I
don't even know how to cancel. They just
make it so hard to do. I might just have
to cancel the credit card.
>> So, there are a couple of things to note
on the quantum front this week. So,
don't
>> has not been solved. By the way, I know
people are asking me, well, did they
solve it this week? No, they didn't.
Galaxy Research has written a report
called optimistically entitled Bitcoin
is rising to the challenge of quantum
readiness. We'll put that in the show
notes.
>> Are we? Are we?
>> In my opinion, it is not. We are not.
they are not. However, Galaxy is a
different perspective. So, we'll let you
decide for yourself.
And then uh there is also a report from
the global risk institute. Uh they do
this quantum survey. So they survey 25
or so sort of top quantum experts,
physicists
and they are plotting a likelihood of a
uh cryptographically relevant quantum
computer. The consensus is about a third
to half think it's going to arrive
within 10 years by 2035.
>> Interesting.
>> Which is an acceleration from prior
years.
>> I sound like a broken record on this,
but just the advancements in artificial
intelligence, it's just so hard to
imagine that won't impact these quantum
timelines.
>> Yeah, without a doubt.
>> Smartest people in the world that can
now work smarter.
>> Yeah. I mean, mathematicians keep
saying, "Wow, I used AI to solve an
unsolved dilemma, right?" or so these
are engineering and physics challenges.
We really think AI will not be able to
contribute there.
>> Yeah, it will.
>> It's obvious. Um Ellanar Tourett just
tweeted a fresh take here. Um quoting
from Cynthia Lumis, we are 99% of the
way there on stable coin yield and
negotiations on the digital asset
portions of the bill are in a good
place. That's really interesting. 99% of
the way there is that's the last big
issue.
>> I am not optimistic that there will be
anything resembling yield when all is
said and done.
>> Well, 99% of the way on stable coin
yield could mean a lot of things. It
could mean that
>> it's thrown in the towel and there is no
yield. But we're 99% of the way sure
that people will agree to that.
>> We're almost at an agreement, but the
agreement may involve no yield.
>> Yes, exactly. Uh last up there is a
group of US regional banks uh including
First Horizon, Mnt and Huntington Bank
shares. They announced plans for Kari
network CI. That is a token tokenized
deposit network built on ZK sync
designed to compete with stable coins.
>> Do you want to know what is not going to
compete with stable coins?
>> What's that?
>> Tokenized deposits.
>> Thought you might say that. Tokenized
deposits are liabilities to the banks
that issue them and they ought not trade
at parody. So Mnt Bank, Huntington Bank
shares, First Horizon, these are not as
creditw worthy as JP Morgan.
>> Yeah. I mean the word US regional banks
should kind of strike fear into your
heart because they almost all failed
just a couple years ago, right? So, why
would you want to go out of your way to
get a tokenized deposit in those banks
versus a fully reserved stable coin?
>> Yes, I get why all these banks want to
do tokenized deposits. It's like I get
why Dwight Trroo in the office wanted to
have a business where he just took one
penny of every transaction. I get why
you'd want that. It doesn't mean it's
going to happen.
>> Yeah. You don't get to have it.
>> So, I And even look, JP Morgan's working
on tokenized deposits. It's obvious why
you'd want it. We want more deposits.
But these things don't have a secondary
market in the real world, and by putting
them on a blockchain doesn't mean
they're going to have a secondary market
magically.
>> Yeah, that one I don't think is going to
make it.
>> Speaking of uh secondary markets and
trading, did you see that big a trade on
Cow Swap last week?
>> Yeah, I'm seeing a lot of theories about
it.
>> Yeah. So, what was it like a
$50 million uh trade
>> with $45 million of slippage?
>> Yeah. Unbelievable. So what the theory
is either it was a fat finger or maybe
this was like a bigger me/moneyaundering
thing.
>> Yeah. I mean I guess uh the idea is if
you have some illicitly acquired funds
which people were rumoring that this guy
was actually known for having
pilered funds from an exchange that you
could look like you were hacked or made
a mistake and then recouped the money on
the back end by running the validator
that collected the me.
So that's the theory at least.
>> I mean, if it was on if it was an
innocent mistake, that is a painful day.
>> That's awful.
>> You just vaporize $45 million.
>> But that's I just don't believe it. Like
if you have $50 million in DeFi, you
probably know how to use Def Swap or a
>> It is. It does call into question some
of just the tools in DeFi. You wouldn't
be able to execute an equity transaction
into an illquid market like that with a
market order on a traditional brokerage.
They make you do a limit order. or they
would you halt you from trading that
stuff. That obviously doesn't exist in
permissionless finance, but maybe some
of these front ends should think about
big red warning signs flashing.
>> Yeah. I'm thinking about Interactive
Brokers. When I want to do an options
trade or something, I have to click
through 10 warning boxes and it doesn't
let me do a market order.
>> Yeah.
>> So,
>> right, it's like buying GBTC like seven,
eight years ago in your IRA. It's like,
are you sure you want to do this? Are
you sure? Are you sure? Are you sure?
It's like, yes, I'm sure.
>> Yeah. and they would put warnings like
you will probably lose almost all your
money on this transaction.
>> But it turns out if you did that with
GBTC back in the day. Uh that was a
great trade.
>> I do remember buying it on the on the
pink sheets.
>> Yeah, that's OTC QX. Yeah.
>> Yeah,
>> those were the days.
>> Those were the days.
>> All right. Well, we're going to go uh
enjoy the sunshine here in Key West.
>> All right. Yeah, another uh another good
rundown. Uh we'll be back next week.
Everybody have a safe and healthy
weekend. We will see you on Monday.